César Maldonado

+57 301 7705464 | cesaramg.14@gmail.com

I'm a full stack web developer with a solid foundation in both front-end and back-end development, and a passion for building innovative web applications. Throughout my career I have successfully developed and deployed full-stack web applications using technologies such as Javascript, React, Node.js, Python and MySQL. Moreover I have experience developing bots with PHP for messaging services using WhatsApp Business API. Some of the projects I have worked on includes a WiFi Hotspot App with Python-Flask, landing pages using React and e-commerce websites using Wordpress.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance

Full Stack Web Developer

January 2021 - Present

- Responsive Web Design: Creating websites that adapt seamlessly to various devices and screen sizes.
- User Experience (UX) Design: Designing intuitive and engaging user interfaces.
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO): Implementing SEO best practices to improve website visibility.
- Web Performance Optimization: Ensuring fast loading times and optimal performance.

Agencia Marítima de Servicios.

Web Developer

September 2018 - December 2020

- Creation, design and management of Company's website.
- Hosting and domain management.
- Wordpress installation, plugin management and server configuration.
- Responsive Web Design.

PORTFOLIO

https://cesaramg14.github.io/Portfolio/

EDUCATION

Electronic Engineer

January 2008 - August 2012

Universidad de Falcón.

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native) English (C1)

COURSES

- Curso de React.JS por Midudev | CURSOREACT.DEV
- The complete React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MySQL developer course | UDEMY
- Front-End Web Developer Bootcamp: HTML, CSS, JS and React | UDEMY
- Docker Essentials | UDEMY
- Introduction to Figma 2024 | UDEMY
- Web Development Masterclass Complete Certificate Course | UDEMY
- Tailwind CSS | UDEMY

SKILLS

Software and Technologies:

- Python, Flask, NodeJS, C#, PHP.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Typescript, Bootstrap, Tailwind.
- Wordpress, Joomla, WooCommerce, Shopify.
- Cloud computing, GIT, SQL, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB, MariaDB, Docker.
- Figma, GIMP, Inkscape, Krita, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator.